weeklydividend.com 2017-06-06

# Born To Sell Privacy Policy

> Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this privacy policy (the "Privacy Policy") explaining how we collect and use personally identifiable information we obtain online and offline from and about individuals located in the U.S. Your use of this Site confirms your acknowledgement and acceptance of the terms of this Privacy Policy.
> 
> The borntosell.com web site, https://www.borntosell.com, ("Borntosell.com" or the "Site") is a general audience web site and is owned and operated by Born To Sell Options, LLC, a Nevada limited liability company ("Born To Sell"). Borntosell.com does not knowingly collect personal identifiable information from children under 13 years of age. All personal identifiable information collected on the Site is owned by Born To Sell.

Visitors, Subscribers, and Members 

> Our Privacy Policy applies to "Visitors," which means that you simply browse the Site, "Subscribers," which means that you have subscribed to receive one or more premium online subscriptions on Borntosell.com (each a "Premium Online Subscription"), and "Members," which means that you have registered with Born To Sell. The term "User" refers to a Visitor, Subscriber or a Member.
> 
> Our Privacy Policy does not apply to those web sites that do not display or link to this Privacy Policy or that have their own privacy statements.

Changes to our Privacy Policy 

> From time to time Born To Sell may revise this Privacy Policy to reflect industry initiatives or changes in the law, our personal identifiable information collection and use practices or the features of the Site or technology. If we make revisions that change the way we collect or use your personal identifiable information, Born To Sell will post those changes in this Privacy Policy and the effective date will be noted at the beginning of such Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the Site after Born To Sell posts a revised Privacy Policy signifies your acceptance of the revised Privacy Policy. Therefore, you should review it periodically so that you are up to date on our most current policies and practices.
> 
> If Born To Sell materially changes its practices regarding collection or use of your personal identifiable information, your personal identifiable information will continue to be governed by the Privacy Policy under which it was collected unless you have been provided notice of, and have not objected to, the change. In the event the last e-mail address you provided to us is not valid or is not capable of delivering the notice to you, Born To Sell's dispatch of an e-mail containing the notice to that e-mail address shall nonetheless constitute effective notice.

What information does Born To Sell collect? 

> **Personally Identifiable Information**
> 
> We only obtain and retain personally identifiable information that you give to us and certain related transactional information we collect based on your use of any password-protected areas of our Site. For example, you might supply your email address by signing up for a free trial of our services, or by contacting us. You also may supply personally identifiable information, including your name, email address and location by signing up for a free trial or by subscribing to our paid services.
> 
> Only subscribers who have passwords are entitled to access the subscribers-only areas of our Site (e.g. Portfolio, Search, and Watchlist). We may collect information concerning the transaction activities of such users when they access a password-protected area of our Site. This transaction information includes information about the portions of our Site such users visits.
> 
> On the Site you may have the opportunity to purchase a Premium Online Subscription. During the subscription process you will be required to provide subscriber data, which may include your e-mail address and zip code. You may be required to provide Personal Financial Information (as defined below in the Privacy Policy) to complete the purchase. If you would like to subscribe or unsubscribe from any Premium Online Subscription refer to our Terms of Use for more information. If you subscribe to any Premium Online Subscription, your subscription will be automatically renewed and the credit card you used to subscribe for such subscription will be charged per the billing cycle of your subscription (e.g. Monthly, Quarterly, Annual), unless you cancel the subscription prior to the renewal date.

> **Non-Personally Identifiable Information**
> 
> When you visit the public parts of our Site, as a User, we do not collect data about who you are or any other personally identifiable information except as described above. We do, however, collect certain non-personally identifiable information about you based upon your activity on our Site. We may collect data about your computer such as operating system type, browser type, and time stamp of visit. This information may include the site's Uniform Resource Locator ("URL") that you just came from, which URL you next go to, what browser you are using, your Internet Protocol ("IP") address, and a list of our Site pages you visit.
> 
> **Aggregate Non-Personally Identifiable Information**
> 
> When you visit the Premium Online Subscription areas of our Site, we may collect "Aggregated Non-Personal Information", which is information that is recorded about users and collected into groups so that it no longer reflects or references an individually identifiable user. We compile and analyze non-personally identifiable information on an aggregated basis. For example, we may know that ninety people visited this Privacy Policy yesterday or how long the average visitor spent at our site last month, but because we do not know their names or addresses they are anonymous to us. We may also use this information to conduct internal research on our visitors' demographics, interests, and behavior to better understand and serve our visitors. We may also collect Aggregate Non-Personal Information from Subscribers and Members concerning their stock and option positions to show common holding or trading trends and post such findings on the Site, in a number of different ways, but the data will be collected and anonymously aggregated and never broken down as to who owns which stocks and options. Aggregate information belongs to Born To Sell, and is not subject to this Privacy Policy.

How does Born To Sell use the information it collects? 

> **Personally Identifiable Information**
> 
> We will not give your data to third parties without your express consent, with the following important exceptions:
> 
>   1. We may be required by law, court order, governmental agency, or law enforcement authority to disclose your personally identifiable information. We may also disclose your information to law enforcement authorities investigating suspected illegal activity.
>   2. If you sign up for one of our free mailing lists or trial subscription, we use your email address to send you email either through our subscription-based mailing lists or to communicate with you about the services we provide.
>   3. We may give your data to trusted third parties, who comply with our privacy policy and confidentiality requirement, for processing your information and assisting in our services (e.g. recurring subscription billing).
> 

> 
> Born To Sell may use an independent third party company to process financial transactions on the Site. When an independent third party company selected by Born To Sell collects, transmits and/or processes your personal financial information, such as your credit card information or other payment information (collectively, "Personal Financial Information"), on the Site it is because you are submitting such Personal Financial Information in order to purchase a subscription to a Premium Online Subscription or purchase any additional services or products offered from time to time on the Site by Born To Sell. Currently, the third party that is collecting, transmitting and/or processing your Personal Financial Information is Authorize.net.
> 
> You must be of the legal age in your State of residence or older to submit Personal Financial Information on the Site, including to place an order on the Site.
> 
> You acknowledge and agree that this Privacy Policy will not apply to any Personal Financial Information that you provide to any independent third party company on the Site and that all payment obligations related to such purchase shall be governed solely by the applicable independent third party company's privacy policy. You further acknowledge and agree that Born To Sell will have no liability for or control over such independent third party company's use or protection of your Personal Financial Information. You should check the privacy policy of the independent third party company's web site to determine how it will handle any Personal Financial Information it collects from you and/or processes.
> 
> You acknowledge and agree that in the event that such independent third party company experiences a data breach that compromises or otherwise affects your Personal Financial Information, Born To Sell shall in no way be responsible or liable to you for such breach. You should contact the applicable independent third party company regarding any such data breach.
> 
> Born To Sell may also share your personal identifiable information with advertisers and business partners that are not affiliated with Born To Sell, but would like to send you information about their products and services. However, you will always have the opportunity to instruct us not to share your information with third parties when identifiable information is collected.
> 
> Born To Sell employees, agents and contractors must have a legitimate business reason to obtain access to your personal identifiable information. Born To Sell may share your personal identifiable information with outside contractors or agents who help us manage our information activities but they may only use your personal identifiable information to provide Born To Sell with a specific service and not for any other purpose.
> 
> Born To Sell may also enter into agreements with outside companies that possess the technology that allows Born To Sell to customize the advertising and marketing messages you receive on the Site. Your non-personal identifiable information and click stream data about your activities on the Site may be shared with these companies so this customization may be accomplished. We require that these companies do not share your information with any third party or use it for any other purpose. Anonymous click stream and demographic information may also be shared with Born To Sell's advertisers and business partners.
> 
> There may be instances when Born To Sell may disclose identifiable information without providing you with a choice in order to protect the legal rights of Born To Sell; to protect the safety and security of visitors to the Site; to protect against fraud or for risk management purposes; or to comply with the law or legal process. In addition, if Born To Sell sells all or part of its business or makes a sale or transfer of assets or is otherwise involved in a merger or business transfer, Born To Sell may transfer your identifiable information to a third party as part of that transaction.

How Born To Sell Uses Cookies 

> The Born To Sell Site requires cookies to function properly. Please enable cookies in your browser if you plan on using this Site.
> 
> Cookies are small data files that are sent from our servers to your computer during a browsing session. In order to make our Site more responsive to the needs of our visitors, we use cookies to assign your Internet browser a unique random number, a sort of anonymous user ID that is stored in a file on your computer. By using a cookie, we are able to automatically identify your browser and track your use of our Site. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies by default, but contain an option for you to turn off the acceptance of cookies if you prefer. You can also delete cookie files from your computer after they have been stored.

Children's Information 

> In compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act and fair information practices, children under the age of 13 are not allowed to sign up for our mailing lists or the subscribers-only portions of our Site. Born To Sell does not intentionally collect any personally identifiable information from children. In addition, Borntosell.com requires that every Subscriber be of the legal age of consent in their respective State of residence.

How do I remove my name from mailing lists or change my information? 

> Subscribers can edit their personal information by logging into the Site with their username/password and then going to the Account tab.
> 
> To unsubscribe to any of our mailing lists, simply log into your account and go to the Email Subscriptions preferences in the Account tab. Uncheck any subscriptions you do not want. You can change your email address in the Account Settings section of the Account tab.
> 
> Otherwise, to change or remove any personally identifiable information you have submitted to us, please contact us at [support@borntosell.com](mailto:support@borntosell.com).
> 
> If for any reason you want Born To Sell to stop using your personal identifiable information, Born To Sell will honor that request; however, Born To Sell will retain any record of your personal identifiable information that is necessary to comply with applicable federal, state or local law. Keep in mind, moreover, that there will be residual information that will remain within Born To Sell's databases, access logs, and other records, which may or may not contain such personal identifiable information. Even after removal of personal identifiable information and user content by you or Born To Sell, personal identifiable information and user content may still be viewable in cached and archived pages or if another User has stored your user content.

What levels of security does Born To Sell have? 

> All communications between your browser and our Site are encrypted with Secure Sockets Layer ("SSL") encryption. Many browsers display a closed padlock icon indicating SSL, and you can also see the URL begins with "https" where the "s" indicates SSL.
> 
> The subscription-only areas of our Site, including Portfolio, Search, and Watchlist, are password-protected and only available to subscribers.
> 
> Born To Sell does not store your credit card information. However, to enable recurring billing for our subscription services, credit card information is stored securely with a third party payment processor who is Payment Card Industry Data Security Standards (PCI DSS) compliant.
> 
> Our Site, and all of the data related to our services, reside on servers maintained by a commercial hosting company. That company takes certain precautions to protect the servers from intrusion, including securing the facilities in which the servers are located and maintaining a firewall to protect against unauthorized access. None of these measures are foolproof; and we do not monitor the web hosting company's facilities or procedures to determine its compliance with the security procedures it says it employs.

How can I reach you? 

> By email: [support@borntosell.com](mailto:support@borntosell.com)
> 
> By phone: (800) 434-6980
> 
> By mail: Born To Sell, 8465 W Sahara, Suite 111-568, Las Vegas, NV 89117
